Oh, I've just never seen anybody do it.
Oh, Ana, great timing.
Here, these chocolates are for you.
These are too.
Oh, wow, thank you.
She's so cute.
Simply adorable.
Libba, maybe I'll just do one more pass.
You've already made five round trips.
Look how many of these I got.
Yeah, isn't that special of you?
What about you?
Me?
I got some for my mom.
A day like any other.
You must be so happy.
February 14th.
Yep, yep, that's great.
That's enough.
Let's end all obligatory chocolates.
We cannot let any more poor unsuspecting guys go getting the wrong idea here.
Okay, you snooze, you lose, guys.
Aren't we calling an end to those?
They're like pigeons.
Hurry up and clear this out.
You take one?
No.
That's yours then.
Figured.
That's why I put them all in your dish.
Huh?
Hmm?
How?
Come on, Yamada.
I'm a boy for the day.
You're such a big glutton.
Whoa!
Dude, look.
This nut here is shaped like a little heart.
Think it might be some secret sign?
Give me a break already.
I shouldn't have gave them anything.
Seriously.
Only takes one little chocolate to give the wrong idea.
Guys are pure like that.
The same goes for you, doesn't it?
You're a pure Cinderella-like guy.
Shut up.
Hmm.
Let's play Shogi today.
I don't really know the rules.
That's fine. We're only playing T-Roll Chocolate Shogi.
Then I definitely don't know the rules.
I never saw that move being played.
Saw what?
You say it too.
I never saw...
Not right now.
Well then when?
Could have all the time in the world and I still wouldn't get this.
Huh? So how do we win?
You win.
Huh?
Here.
The winner takes all the pieces.
That's the rule.
Now is the time.
What now?
Thank you.
Chocolate.
These are chocolates.
They definitely are.
Let me see your chocolate.
Yours has no heart.
It's just an obligatory one.
See?
I don't want to get the wrong idea like him.
Jeez.
Should have just went with ones that said obligatory on them.
Yeah, just go giving random chocolates to boys and expect them to get it, huh?
Gotta make it clear how you really feel.
All right, I'll see you later.
Bye!
Chocolate.
More than that.
The fact she'd even give away any snack is a miracle.
Is this just her being unpredictable again?
How am I supposed to run like this?
This is for you.
Wow, thanks.
I'm jealous.
You can't get all the chocolate, you know.
That's not it.
She's extra unpredictable today.
It's just, why make a big deal about giving them out at school?
I mean, Hara and Kanzaki walk together and they go on...
They go on dates, don't they?
She can give them to him whenever.
There are plenty of hours in the day.
School is a place of learning.
And no, I'm not just jealous.
Anyway.
See ya, huh?
Give me a lift.
Riding sideways is scary.
Slow down a little.
There are plenty of hours in the day.
We're at it again, aren't we?
I thought I was dead when we rode by that police box last time.
I didn't even notice.
I thought about telling you to get off when we were closing in on it.
Afraid of a little bit of change, aren't you?
But I couldn't after you just came out and said that.
Did I really say that?
Pretty sure those were your exact words.
You live for change, you live for change, so you wouldn't get it.
True.
Oh, I think I understand now.
Maybe it's because I'm so happy now.
Not just yet.
I still need more.
I mean, I'm still hungry.
This stuff sure is pricey, huh?
You got the chocolate bun?
Didn't you get a bunch of chocolate today from the year one, girls?
It's fine, though.
I can eat chocolate forever.
That bag's full of obligatory chocolates.
Don't look!
I wasn't!
So today, did you get...
Huh?
No, uh...
Well, uh...
So what sort of chocolate would make you think that it actually meant something?
Um, that's a tough one.
I might not know unless I was told it was.
It would be tough otherwise.
Oh, people might get the wrong idea if it was heart-shaped.
According to Arachi, at least.
It's on your face.
See ya!
For a second...
I think I really got my hopes up.
I might not know unless I was told it was.
Hmm...
Hmmm...
Hmm....
Hmm...
Uh...
는이...
Hmm...
Um, you're still here
Come on, you can do this. So hey for you
Back in class you said that you are a guy today
I'm a boy for the day
Later then
Good that's it good thinking that was the right move. This is Yamada. We're talking about
No, that was definitely weird
Something called melty kiss
I'm afraid to look
February 14th
Hey
7 26 p.m
It's really kind of funny. I thought I'd change one Taro's walking course today. Hey
And before I knew it. I realized that we were close by your house. Let's talk. Okay. Oh sure
Wanna hold sure that's okay
Whoa, whoa
Be sure to hold it down
There you have it right
Okay
Time to gamble
The hot cocoa I want and the bitter black coffee I definitely do not
Pressed at the exact same time for the thrill of it
You call that gambling?
Go
Press them both at the same time
Here you can have this if you want what thanks
So then she of all people comes running around and it's all like leave those bees
And then after that you're acting weird today something's off
I'm always weird though
That's true. Whoa. Hey now
But you said it yourself
She's always calling me a weirdo, but she's not around right now. So I said it for her instead
I see
You're cold out here. No, I'm okay
Thanks for the chocolate. Oh, yeah
Sure, it's warm this year, huh?
Yeah, sure
Guess it's not gonna snow
What are we doing?
I-Ichi
Huh?
Did you maybe um get any chocolate today other than from family? Huh?
Here
That's the rule
Now is the time
You have it
I didn't
Yeah
Um, did you uh give anyone any?
Huh?
That's safe to ask, right?
Nope
I decided not to give out any obligatory ones
Oh, yeah
The winner takes all the pieces
You have it
Well, I agree with Arachi that we should get rid of obligatory chocolates
All it does is give dumb guys the wrong idea
That bitter?
Huh?
I was lying when I said I didn't like sweet stuff
Here, then I have uh
Huh?
Uh
I-I'm afraid that I um made it a little too sweet, see?
What?
Split
Huh?
Thanks for splitting this
It's okay
You can get the wrong...
...idea
YAMARAS
Huh?
What?
Why?
I wasn't able to get it right
Any of it
This is actually good
No, I mean what I'm trying to tell you is this is really good
YAMARAS
Well, then
You need to give me a hug for it
Uh
YAMARAS
BLAIGS
Oh
Mmw
What's with the intense face you got there?
What am I going to give her for White Day?
That's still a whole month away.
No.
You could say we only have one month left.
That's right.
I got chocolate from Yamada.
I sure did.
Am I going to be able to give her something good for White Day in return?
What's important now is me and this one month.
Dude, all you got were the chocolate Sekine gave everyone in class.
But mine had a heart-shaped nut in it.
Girls want you to pick up on stuff like that.
You should go set that idiot straight, Moe.
You know, I think.
I'll let you figure out what it meant, yes.
That's just cruel.
Uh-huh.
I'd really love some earpods for myself.
I really want to get her something that makes her scream.
You're amazing.
What could Taze take me?
I'll even take Runner Up.
Guy wants a whole fan club.
I got it.
Some sexy lingerie.
What made you even think that?
I got handmade chocolate, so...
Handmade lingerie.
I don't think it works that way, bro.
I'm thinking I might go for an all-you-can-eat snack buffet for White Day.
Oh, that's actually a pretty good idea.
Huh?
Although, inviting her out is the hard part, I think.
Hold on!
Someone gave chocolate to you!
Shoot!
Well, um, yeah.
No point in lying.
Whatever!
Bet she's butt ugly!
Uh-huh.
All right, pass over here, guys.
Over here!
Hey, I'm open!
Get in!
Well, I mean...
If you don't really like her at all, who cares what you get her for White Day?
That's not true.
I like the girls that like me.
It's better to have as many chances as you can, right?
Too bad you have none.
I realize, though, I don't know a single thing about Sekine.
That's what really scares me.
I can't half-ass this.
That's surprising.
So where are we even going right now?
Oh!
Hey!
Huh?
So Nanjo here sits on the student committee with me.
What?
This guy's fading out of existence.
He's got all the ladies, so we should totally get his advice.
He's still alive?
I don't get all the ladies.
Like I believe that.
Honestly, I just have a sense for when I have a chance.
Can tell when the mood's right, you know?
No, you can't.
Hmm?
This guy was apparently given some valentine chocolate, too.
So we were wondering what to give back.
Oh?
Got some, did ya?
The problem is, I don't really know what my girl actually likes.
Think I should figure that out before doing anything first?
Nah, man.
No point in doing that.
I mean, after all, guys and girls can never really know each other, honestly.
Oh yeah, I guess you're right.
You think so?
They're a whole different animal.
Different upbringing, different tastes, different values.
But when you get to know them, you find what you have in common.
I mean, finding what you can share or understand about each other is what's important, I'd say.
So, yeah, uh, what kind of present should we get then?
Heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh.
What about lingerie?
Righty-o!
I totally knew it!
I'm sure they will love whatever you get them.
Won't they, Ichihara?
What a lame trap.
Yeah!
I knew he was the right guy to ask about these things!
You believe that?
Give yourself some credit for helping me learn and realize more stuff than he does.
Hey, you're not going to win me over here!
Uh, gotta get to practice!
I'm going home.
Oh!
Hellooo!
Cut it out!
Oh!
Is that all right?
Hmm?
All right, throwing it over there.
Here we go!
Hmm.
Nope!
Hmm!
Huh?
Huh.
Hmmmmmm...
I...
I really like...
Yamada.
Whew!
Yaw możliwe
Mm.
Easy.
Oh, see ya!